# Sara George

Lancaster, OH 43130 segeorge0518@sbcglobal.net +1 740 215 9529

# **Professional Summary**

Customer service and merchandising specialist with years of experience with prior work history in a fast-paced warehouse environment. Detail oriented, reliable, and a fast learner with a passion for new learning experiences.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

# Work Experience

# **Night Stocker and Merchandise Service Associate**

Lowes Home Improvement-Lancaster, OH August 2020 to August 2021

As a Night Stock Associate job duties entailed the following:

- · Bringing pallets of merchandise to the floor and restocking of shelves.
- $\cdot$  Putting remaining product in appropriate overstock locations and correctly marking product boxes with item number and quantity.
- $\cdot$  Locating new products and setting them aside for departments to determine where the appropriate location will be.
- · Upon completion of other duties job focus shifted to assisting day shift duties where able. This included, but was not limited to, moving new displays out to the floor for quicker construction, filling coolers and snack shelves located at registers, front facing product, locating misplaced product and returning it to it's location, and bringing down pallets from overstock to be broken down or if department requested it be brought down for them.

After transferring to Merchandise Service Associate duties changed to

- · Assembled and constructed product displays such as standard product displays as instructed by cooperate partners, promotional sales displays, holiday displays.
- · Ensuring constructed displays remained clean, checking them for damage, and that they remained in high traffic areas for maximum customer interaction.
- $\cdot$  Checking planograms to ensure product is located where is should be in the store and is in it's designated location on the shelf.
- · Responded to product inventory changes by not only ensuring shelves were stocked, but by resetting shelves to new planograms. This included changes in the shelving fixtures themselves such as the addition, removal, or height adjustment of shelf elevations.
- · Ensuring products were correctly priced and making new labels where necessary.
- · Adjusted inventory stock in the system in response to known lost or damaged inventory.
- · Organization of overstock.

#### **Fufillment Associate**

Amazon-Etna, OH

October 2019 to July 2020

 $\cdot$  Received and stocked items, and record data using proprietary computer systems in preparation for order fulfillment.

- · Checked merchandise for damages, and ensured product integrity.
- · Brought pallets of product to other associates to stock.
- · Cleaned and maintain supplies, tools, equipment, and storage areas in order to ensure compliance with safety regulations.

### **Customer Service Specialist**

Dicks Sporting Goods-Lancaster, OH February 2019 to August 2019

- Provided excellent customer service by greeting all customers and directing them to products they are seeking.
- Making sure upon check-out that customers were able to get all the products they were looking for. If unable to do so, offer to see if we were able to order the product for the customer.
- Addressed questions and concerns both in person and over the phone, or ensured that the customer was directed to another associate capable of answering questions if unable to.
- · Processed returns and refunds.
- Assessed the condition of retuned merchandise, and, if acceptable, prepared it to be returned to sales floor.
- Provide product coupons, informational pamphlets, or other incentives to persuade people to buy products. This included suggesting the stores rewards program and offering applications for the stores line of credit.
- Kept physical record of amount of new rewards program members, credit card applicants, sales of items to be held for customers, and special orders that included installations.

#### **Student Assistant**

Oxley's By the Numbers Cafe at The Ohio State University-Columbus, OH October 2018 to December 2018

- Prepare menu items, such as sandwiches, hot or cold beverages such as coffee, espresso drinks, blended coffees, and teas.
- Logged data on cleaning and sanitization times, freezer temperatures, and holding temperature of prepared foods.
- Receive and process customer payments.
- Restock product displays such as drink coolers, bakery goods case, and grab-and-go items cooler.
- Ensured the cleanliness of the café through regular cleaning of food preparation spaces, utensils, and seating area, and prevention of food cross contamination.

#### Cashier

Mejer-Lancaster, OH August 2014 to November 2014

- · Receive and process payment
- $\cdot$  Provide product samples, coupons, informational brochures, or other incentives to persuade people to buy products.
- · Suggest specific product purchases to meet customers' needs.

#### Temporary receptionist/Executive Assistant

M-Engineering-Westerville, OH June 2013 to July 2013

- · Answer phone calls and direct calls to appropriate parties or take messages.
- · Manage and maintain executives' schedules.
- · Greet visitors and determine whether they should be given access to specific individuals.
- $\cdot$  Prepare memos, letters, and other documents, using word processing software, spreadsheets, and databases.

- $\cdot \ \text{Perform general office duties, such as ordering supplies, maintaining records management database systems, and performing basic bookkeeping work.}$
- · Make travel arrangements for associates
- · Log the use of certain materials and equipment if associate was traveling for land survey.
- $\cdot$  Prepare agendas and make arrangements, such as coordinating catering for luncheons, vacations, meetings, and logging sick time.

## Education

# **Bachelor of Arts in Japanese**

The Ohio State University-Columbus, OH December 2018

## Skills

- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Office
- Data entry
- Merchandising
- Administrative experience
- Microsoft Powerpoint
- Customer service
- Warehouse experience
- Windows
- Microsoft Word